acceleratedmentoring.net 2013-01-22

# Welcome to eLibrary 3.0

**Accelerated Mentoring Privacy Policy  
Last Revised October 27, 2010**

This is the Privacy Policy for the Accelerated Mentoring website (the "Site"), which is operated by Accelerated Mentoring LLC ("we" or "us"). This Privacy Policy applies only to the Site and not to other websites or services operated by Accelerated Mentoring or its subsidiaries or affiliates. 

Your privacy is very important to us and we are committed to protecting it. We understand that you need to be in control of your personal information. This Privacy Policy explains the manner in which we collect personal information from you and the purpose for that collection. This Privacy Policy is designed to ensure that you are aware of how your personal information is being used and to provide you with choices about that use. By visiting the Site or submitting your personal information, you accept the terms described in this Privacy Policy. 

**1\. COLLECTION OF PERSONAL INFORMATION**   
We collect information that identifies you, such as names, postal addresses, and e-mail addresses ("personal information"), when voluntarily submitted. We receive and store any information that you choose to enter through the Site, including any submissions that you make or content you provide on or through the Site. 

We do not knowingly collect information from minors. Should we learn that a minor has provided us with personal information, we will delete that information from our database. 

**2\. AUTOMATED INFORMATION COLLECTIONS**   
A cookie is a string of information that is sent by a website and stored on your hard drive or temporarily in your computer's memory. We may employ cookie technology to identify you, track your use of the Site, to help you move faster through our Site, to estimate our total audience size and traffic, and to help us improve our Site's experience by measuring which site areas are of greatest interest to users. You can turn off the ability to receive any of these cookies by adjusting the browser in your computer, but you should note that disabling cookies in your browser may also prevent other w ebsites from placing cookies on your computer. If you do this, it may materially affect the functionality of the Site and the information you can access through it. 

We collect data when you visit most pages on the Site. Your visit may automatically provide us with data about your computer, such as your IP (Internet Protocol) address, browser type, operating system, domain name, access times, and referring website addresses. 

We use this automated data to obtain general statistics regarding the use of the Site and its specific web pages and to evaluate how our visitors use and navigate the Site on an aggregate basis. 

**3\. HOW WE USE YOUR INFORMATION**   
We may use the information we collect about you in connection with providing services offered on the Site, including in the following ways: 

  * For the purpose for which you specifically provided the personal information, for example, to respond to a specific inquiry.
  * To send you notifications about your accounts or transactions with us and to otherwise contact you with information that we believe will be of interest to you.
  * To analyze our business or use of the Site, enhance existing features, or develop new features products and services.
  * As otherwise described to you at the point of collection.

**4\. SHARING WITH THIRD PARTIES**   
We may share the information we collect about you in the following limited circumstances: 

  * With service providers that perform certain functions on our behalf, including processing information that you provide to us on the Site, operating the Site or portions of it, or in connection with other aspects of our business.
  * To selected third party accounting firms whose products or services you might find interesting or helpful in your business.
  * To respond to subpoenas, court orders, or other legal process, in response to a request for cooperation from law enforcement or another government agency, to investigate, prevent, or take action regarding illegal activities, suspected fraud, or to enforce our user agreement or this Privacy Policy, or to protect our rights or the rights of others.
  * In connection with a corporate transaction involving Accelerated Mentoring.
  * As otherwise described to you at the point of collection or pursuant to your consent.

**5\. YOUR ABILITY TO CHOOSE**   
You can let us know, upfront and at no cost, that you do not wish us to share your information with third parties for marketing purposes or to notify you about our own products and services and special offers by sending us a written request by writing to Accelerated Mentoring LLC, Attn: Privacy Policy Issues, P.O. Box 767, Boise, Idaho 83701. 

**6\. SECURITY**   
We care about protecting the security of your personal information, and we have implemented security procedures to protect the personal information that you provide to us. However, no method of transmitting or storing electronic data is ever completely secure, and we cannot guarantee that such information will never be accessed, used, or released in a manner that is inconsistent with this policy. 

**7\. LINKS TO OTHER WEBSITES**   
We may make content or services from other websites, including our affiliated or co-branded websites, available to you from links located on this Site. These other websites are not subject to this Privacy Policy. We recommend that you review the privacy policy at each such website to determine how that site protects your privacy. 

**8\. CHANGES TO THIS POLICY**   
From time to time we may modify this Privacy Policy. We will notify you of any material change by sending a notice to the e-mail address you provided to us or by placing a notice on the Site. You can view the most recent version of the Privacy Policy at any time by clicking the "Privacy Policy" link at the bottom of pages on the Site. Your continued use of the Site after any modification indicates your agreement to the new terms. 

**9\. HOW YOU CAN CONTACT US**   
If you have any questions or concerns about this Privacy Policy, including the review and update of the personal information you have provided Accelerated Mentoring, you may write to us at Accelerated Mentoring LLC, Attn: Privacy Policy Issues, P.O. Box 767, Boise, Idaho 83701.
